export const chapter = "Chapter - 9: The Struggle ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What ambition did Booker T. Washington have from a young age?",
          optionA: "To become a coal miner",
          optionB: "To work as a janitor",
          optionC: "To go to Hampton Institute",
          correctAnswer: "To go to Hampton Institute",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How did Booker T. Washington fund his journey to Hampton Institute?",
          optionA: "He had enough money saved up.",
          optionB: "He borrowed money from a friend.",
          optionC: "He relied on assistance from family and neighbors.",
          correctAnswer: "He relied on assistance from family and neighbors.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What job did Booker T. Washington take at Mrs. Ruffner's house?",
          optionA: "Teacher",
          optionB: "Janitor",
          optionC: "Chef",
          correctAnswer: "Janitor",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How did Booker T. Washington prove his worthiness to the head teacher at Hampton Institute?",
          optionA: "By excelling in a written exam",
          optionB: "By sweeping and cleaning a recitation room",
          optionC: "By paying a large sum of money",
          correctAnswer: "By sweeping and cleaning a recitation room",
        },
        {
          question: "What was the cost of boarding at Hampton Institute?",
          optionA: "$5 per month",
          optionB: "$10 per month",
          optionC: "$70 per year",
          correctAnswer: "$10 per month",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How did Booker T. Washington manage to get books while at Hampton Institute?",
          optionA: "He borrowed books from his classmates.",
          optionB: "He received books as gifts from his teachers.",
          optionC: "He collected and created his own library.",
          correctAnswer: "He collected and created his own library.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What valuable lesson did Booker T. Washington learn at Hampton Institute regarding personal hygiene?",
          optionA: "The importance of using cologne",
          optionB: "The significance of wearing fine clothing",
          optionC: "The value of bathing for health and self-respect",
          correctAnswer: "The value of bathing for health and self-respect",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How did Booker T. Washington manage to pay for his boarding and tuition at Hampton Institute?",
          optionA: "He received financial aid from the government.",
          optionB: "He worked as a janitor in exchange for room and board.",
          optionC: "His family sent him enough money to cover the expenses.",
          correctAnswer:
            "He worked as a janitor in exchange for room and board.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What challenge did Booker T. Washington face regarding clothing at Hampton Institute?",
          optionA: "He had too many clothes to choose from.",
          optionB: "He struggled to find clothes that fit him.",
          optionC: "He had to wear the same suit of clothes continuously.",
          correctAnswer:
            "He had to wear the same suit of clothes continuously.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What was the significance of the barrels from the North to Hampton students like Booker T. Washington?",
          optionA: "They contained food supplies.",
          optionB: "They held second-hand clothing for students in need.",
          optionC: "They were used as educational tools.",
          correctAnswer: "They held second-hand clothing for students in need.",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Booker T. Washington faced numerous difficulties in obtaining an education, including working in a coalmine and as a janitor. He resolved to go to the Hampton Institute, despite not knowing its location, because he was constantly on fire with the ambition to go to Hampton. This thought was with him day and night. He continued to work for a few months longer in the coalmine and then worked as a domestic help in the household of General Lewis Ruffner.",
          optionA: "ambition",
          optionB: "determination",
          optionC: "motivation",
          correctAnswer: "ambition",
        },
        {
          question:
            "While working in the coalmine, Booker T. Washington learned about the Hampton Normal and Agricultural Institute in Virginia, meant for black people. He decided to join it one day. He continued to work for a few months longer in the coalmine and then worked as a domestic help in the household of General Lewis Ruffner.",
          optionA: "the opportunity",
          optionB: "the option",
          optionC: "the decision",
          correctAnswer: "the decision",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Booker T. Washington worked at the household of Mrs. Viola Ruffner, who was known for being very strict with her servants. He learned that she wanted everything kept clean, things done promptly and systematically, and absolute honesty and frankness. He also had an opportunity to go to school for an hour in the day during winter months.",
          optionA: "cleanliness",
          optionB: "strictness",
          optionC: "discipline",
          correctAnswer: "cleanliness",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Booker T. Washington prepared to go to the Hampton Institute, even though he had no definite idea of its location or the cost of getting there. He resolved to make an effort with the assistance of his family members and neighbors.",
          optionA: "plan",
          optionB: "journey",
          optionC: "goal",
          correctAnswer: "plan",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Booker T. Washington reached Hampton after a long journey with various challenges. He considered the large, three-story, brick school building to be the largest and most beautiful building he had ever seen, and it felt like he had reached the Promised Land.",
          optionA: "accomplishment",
          optionB: "destination",
          optionC: "dream",
          correctAnswer: "destination",
        },
        {
          question:
            "After reaching Hampton, Booker T. Washington presented himself before the head teacher for assignment to a class. He didn't make a very favorable impression because he had been without proper food, a bath, and change of clothing for a long time.",
          optionA: "appearance",
          optionB: "attitude",
          optionC: "presentation",
          correctAnswer: "appearance",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The head teacher asked Booker T. Washington to sweep the adjoining recitation room. He saw this as an opportunity and swept the room thoroughly, impressing the teacher with his dedication to cleanliness.",
          optionA: "challenge",
          optionB: "favor",
          optionC: "chance",
          correctAnswer: "chance",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The sweeping of the recitation room was Booker T. Washington's college examination, and it paved the way for him to get through Hampton. Miss Mary F. Mackie, the head teacher, offered him a position as the janitor.",
          optionA: "success",
          optionB: "entrance",
          optionC: "scholarship",
          correctAnswer: "entrance",
        },
        {
          question:
            "While at Hampton, Booker T. Washington realized the value of a bath, not only in keeping the body healthy but also in inspiring self-respect and promoting virtue.",
          optionA: "cleanliness",
          optionB: "hygiene",
          optionC: "sanitation",
          correctAnswer: "hygiene",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Booker T. Washington, while at Hampton, had to wear one suit of clothes continually and keep it clean. He managed to get some second-hand clothing sent in barrels from the North, which proved a blessing to many deserving students.",
          optionA: "garments",
          optionB: "apparel",
          optionC: "attire",
          correctAnswer: "apparel",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "Hampton Institute is located in Virginia.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Booker T. Washington worked as a janitor at the coalmine.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Mrs. Viola Ruffner was known for being lenient with her servants.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Booker T. Washington had proper clothing when he first reached Hampton.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The head teacher at Hampton immediately admitted Booker T. Washington as a student.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Booker T. Washington's future at Hampton was dependent on the cleanliness of a room.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Miss Mary F. Mackie was not a supportive figure in Booker T. Washington's life at Hampton.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Booker T. Washington believes that education from books and costly apparatus is superior to learning from great men and women.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Booker T. Washington's tuition cost at Hampton was seventy dollars a year.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Second-hand clothing sent in barrels from the North proved to be a burden for Booker T. Washington.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
